<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<application>
 <id type="desktop">org.qupzilla.QupZilla.desktop</id>
 <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
 <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
 <name>QupZilla</name>
 <summary>Web Browser</summary>
 <description>
  <p>
    QupZilla is a new and very fast QtWebKit browser. It aims to be a lightweight web browser available through all major platforms. This project has been originally started only for educational purposes. But from its start, QupZilla has grown into a feature-rich browser.
  </p>
  <p>
    QupZilla has all standard functions you expect from a web browser. It includes bookmarks, history (both also in sidebar) and tabs. Above that, you can manage RSS feeds with an included RSS reader, block ads with a built-in AdBlock plugin, block Flash content with Click2Flash and edit the local CA Certificates database with an SSL manager.
  </p>
  <p>
    QupZilla's main aim is to be a very fast and very stable QtWebKit browser available to everyone. There are already a lot of QtWebKit browsers available, but they are either bound to the KDE environment, not actively developed or very unstable and miss important features. QupZilla, a multi-platform, modern and actively developed browser, is here to fill this gap by providing a very stable browsing experience.
  </p>
 </description>
 <screenshots>
  <screenshot type="default" width="871" height="568">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/gnome_window.png</screenshot>
  <screenshot width="948" height="638">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_window.png</screenshot>
  <screenshot width="864" height="567">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/dial_gnome.png</screenshot>
  <screenshot width="944" height="633">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_speeddial.png</screenshot>
  <screenshot width="809" height="528">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/preferences_gnome.png</screenshot>
  <screenshot width="760" height="518">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_preferences.png</screenshot>
 </screenshots>
 <url type="homepage">https://www.qupzilla.com/</url>
 <updatecontact>nowrep_at_gmail.com</updatecontact>
</application>
